Uh, congratulations. Uh, just tell us
about the talks you may have had with
the Bucks and and your opportunity to
come in here as an ex receiver. Of
course, they lost Mike Evans who's a
potential Hall of Famer one day, but
just the opportunity that that you would
have at that position.
>> Yeah, man. You know, um, you know, Mike
Evans a great player, great leader. you
know, he he he definitely, you know,
brought some game to that organization
and, you know, just having that
opportunity, you know, to be picked
after him or looked after him as a guy
who know who can, you know, potentially
come in and make those same plays, man,
I don't take that for granted at all,
you know. Um, I definitely say just from
day one, you know, meeting the coaches
on the Zoom call, they definitely were
interested and they communicated after
and I know they they showed a lot of
interest, man. I you know I did I I
wouldn't say I knew where I was going at
specifically, but I had a I had I had
this little feeling, you know, maybe I
had a chance.
>> You talked about the Senior Bowl
experience and how important that was
for you to go there and really show out
as a smaller school guy from Georgia
State.
>> Yeah. Is you talking about the Senior
Bowl, right?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah. Yes, sir. man, just being, you
know, being looked at as people value
and being able to come in and, you know,
learn learn from coaches, you know, who
are who great at their position. They
know, you know, the ins and out of the
game. I say, you know, just getting that
experience and compete a bit compete
against guys who are also in this draft
and, you know, considered the best guys
in the world stepping into this league.
You know, like I said, I don't take
anything for thing for granted and I
just try to leave my mark wherever I go
at. Can you talk about your decision to
stay at Georgia uh and not go and
transfer to one of those other schools
when you had offers?
>> Yeah. Um unfortunately I was you know
with the agency and um my mom wasn't
really feeling their representation and
how they go about things. Luckily I was
surrounded by great people who who have
my best interest I'll say. And you know,
we kind of just talked about the pros
and the cons of everything in my
situation. You know, and you know, the
what if and what and you know, you can
do this from Georgia State. You know,
you can set set the pay for Georgia
State and be the biggest guy to come
from there. And you know, I wore that on
my sleeve and I knew who I was and I I
knew regardless of where I'm at, you
know, the NFL will find me. My mom was
like, you know, don't chase the money,
son. The money's going to come.
>> Yeah. Not a lot of Georgia State
products in the NFL, but there's already
one here in Tampa in Venture.
>> Big Ben.
>> What's it going to be like to reunite
with him and have familiar face when you
get here?
>> Yeah, definitely. I know he, you know,
picked it up and he has been blessed to
make the opportunity at a 53 man roster.
So, you know, if I could soak up any
game just from an older guy, I know he
kind of, you know, probably going about
the right way to handle his business. If
I could soak up any knowledge from him,
definitely looking forward to that.
you've made a lot of catches of 20 plus
yards. Um, you know, giving your team an
opportunity to score very quickly, you
know. Um, just what what's that like for
you when you have the ability to just in
in a split second, you know, change kind
of the trajectory of a game, the outcome
of a game with one big play? What's that
like for you?
>> Yeah, man. I say my prep preparation
coming into the game, you know, I I try
those things. I practice really hard.
you know, you know, when the opportunity
comes, I feel like I excel. You know,
luckily, I've been surround surrounded
by great people who who had my best
interest, and you know, my game was
definitely not founded, and they helped
me polish polish my game.
>> Where did your contested catch ability
come from? How did you hone that?
>> Yeah, I'll say that that's more so of,
you know, playing multi sports, playing
basketball a lot. I'm a big fan of
basketball and, you know, just being a
guy who goes up and get the ball as a
rebound. That's kind of how I think of,
you know, just a jump ball. I'll say,
>> as far as wide receivers in the NFL or
or older guys, who who are some of the
guys you study? Who are some of the guys
you watch that you maybe model your game
after?
>> I say T. Higgins, you know, uh, George
Pickkins. Um, I like J Mo a lot. you
know, a lot of those big guys who can
move in and out their in and out their
breaks, you know, go get the ball at the
same time, maybe catch it at the line of
scrimmage and, you know, take it to the
house.
>> Ted Ted, what are your thoughts on
catching the football next season from
Baker Mayfield,
>> man? Man, I I I haven't took a a chance
to grasp that in yet. And you know, when
I get the opportunity to get there, you
know, I'm I'mma be plugged to him and
I'm and I'm gonna take, you know,
advantage of every opportunity I get.
>> We got Chris Godwin in the wide receiver
room, IA, Jaylen McMillan, some of those
other guys. How excited are you to kind
of learn from Chris Godwin and some of
these other guys who've had success in
the league, especially someone like
Amecha Ibuka and TZ Johnson who both had
success early on as rookies.
>> Yeah, man. coming into this thing, you
know, the best feedback I got was from
these coaches is, you know, stick to
that older guy who does the thing right
and and I was really big on, you know, I
want to come in and have immediate
success. So, you know, I'm I'm going to
stay in their hip pocket, maybe be a
little annoying at the same time, but I
know, you know, these are probably great
guys in the room and they're great
leaders and and I look up look forward
to looking up to those guys and I know I
know that's going to help me, you know,
expand my game.
>> Back to the senior role. What was really
an opportunity for you to face tougher
competition? Like what was the mentality
that you needed to have that allowed you
to to success because to have success?
Because you know some people they can
get overwhelmed in those moments and
sometimes they can kind of wilt under
that pressure but for you it seemed like
you really flourished.
>> Yeah man. I say I'm I'm big in my Bible.
You know I took that morning and I
prayed that day before I even hit the
field and I knew everything was in God's
hands. you know, uh, you know, I I
prepare myself well for for those
moments and I've been through, you know,
situations, close games, tight games
and, you know, I know what it feels like
to lose and, um, so anything, you know,
I do, you know, I I do it to my best
ability and I know, you know, how to how
to go about things and I feel like if I
give my all, you know, I'm comfortable
with that.
>> What are some of your biggest strengths
and biggest things you're bringing to
this roster, do you think?
Yeah, I I feel like, you know, I'm a
true big body X receiver, but I also can
play any anywhere on the field and I'm
dynamic. You know, I'm I'm a team player
at the same time. If you're asking me to
do any role or play any position, I'm
going to I'm going to step in and, you
know, do my part.
>> How are you celebrating the draft? Who
are you with today? And and how's it
gone for you?
>> Yeah, about 40 to 50 family members,
close friends that I grew up with. my
family, you know. I'm really big on my
family, my household, my grandma and
cousins and all. They're they're out
here and they're excited, man. More
maybe more excited than me.
>> Yeah. What was the reaction like when
you got the phone call?
>> Definitely considering your school's
history.
>> Yeah. Yeah, definitely. Before I even
picked up the phone, they already were
like pulling out the cameras. They're
running up like everybody just getting
ready and excited for the moment. Uh,
actually I already had got the call
before I even, you know, got the chance
to see it on TV. So, they were already
causing havoc in in the Airbnb and the
party and all of that. They were they
were going crazy.
>> Ted Ted, I'm actually Georgia State
class of 2018, so I'm excited to have
you come down here. Um,
>> okay.
>> You are now.
>> Hell yeah. You already know what it is,
man. Uh,
>> so you are the highest drafted player in
Georgia State football history. Now,
just to come from Georgia State, make
history like that, what does it mean to
you, especially a program that I know
showed you a lot of love the last couple
years?
>> Yeah, man. I give a shout out to, you
know, coach Dale McGee and and my
receiver coach Damian Craig, also to
Quan Marshall, my assistant receiver,
coach, man. They they they had a plan
for me and they told me how they felt
about me just coming there. They were
truth truthful from the beginning and
they saw the potential with me and you
know they stick stick with me every day
and glued to me whether it's words of
encouragements or words words I needed
to hear.
>> Ted, if you had a message for the Bucks
fans watching this right now, what would
it be?
>> Man, y'all got y'all got a dog. I'm
telling you you like I seen all these
people saying sleep at a drive, man. I'm
I'm here for a reason.
>> Awesome. Anything else?
>> All right, guys. Congrats.
Thank you, God.
>> Definitely.
>> We'll see you in a couple weeks.
>> Jesus day. Yes, sir.